A special treat from Prod Vietnam
to all esteemed guests
present at today's special event,
Vuong Tien Investment.  Good
afternoon toish guest and
welcome all
my name is Lure
afternoon.   This
clearly shows that the market
still has a lot of potential, with many
positive signs, right?  And just now
I saw a hierarchy of needs, and from
a customer's perspective, I
saw many points
within it, so I can tentatively conclude that
customer demand clearly shows
potential, and the industry has
abundant room for growth.  So, I'd like to ask for
your perspective on
Fredential Vietnam's next strategic direction to
meet this customer need
?  Please come in.
Typically, when customers buy
insurance, they have to make trade-offs, for example,
better protection benefits
come at a higher cost, right?  However,
in Pro Vinh Tien's case, the
insurance benefits are better, but
the cost is actually
more favorable.  Then I guess we'll have to ask Mr. Linh to
share more specific details about this point.  That
's the perfect answer to
those burning questions—a
very hot topic that customers
clearly need but haven't had a
concrete answer to yet, right?  And that's
why, throughout its
nearly 30-year journey in Vietnam, Vietnam has always
been a leading brand, right
?
Why?   Yeah
.